Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ apoorvapatil9295 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Strategic Sourcing
Niche Talent Acquisition
Client Relations

APOORVA PATIL

Recruiter at Microsoft

Bengaluru

Summary

Open Opportunities @ Microsoft CSEO Teams in Hyderabad Connect with me to explore open opportunities with Microsoft IDC teams.

Looking for Software Development Engineers (3 - 10 years), who have strong passion towards technology, great problem-solving skills, strong background in computer science (Data Structures, Algorithms) and solid understanding of Object-Oriented Design and Concept

Experience

Microsoft

Recruiter

January 2020 - Present (8 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

As a part of Global Talent Acquisition Team,

Hiring Talents all over India across levels

Majorly working on software development requirements

Partnering with Hiring managers to understand the requirements and work on it

DM me to know more on the opportunities that you are looking for.

CareerNet Technologies

Associate Consultant

May 2018 - November 2019 (1 year 7 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

I recruit for Technical requirements for top product-based, captives, startup ups based in and around Bangalore.

Hiring for the positions like:

Technical Architects
Solution Architects
Windows/Vmware Admin
Salesforece Developer/Admin
Leads/Managerial positions

Reach me at patilapoorva163@gmail.com or just DM me on the same account for those who are looking out for job change.

Qwikcilver Solutions Intern May 2017 - July 2017 (3 months) Bengaluru Area, India

Education

PES University

Human Resources Management/Personnel Administration, General · (2016 - 2018)